OK, once recording has started,
once the post load is done,
let me know like I will stop the
recording and restart before jumping into
any Yeah, yeah,
whatever related to batch notifications
added handling within the batch task flow.
I'll cover everything now post it
whatever parameter file make we can take
it in a separate batch post load.
So this is here.
The system cheques the final status of
the of all the jobs under that given
batch.
So if all the jobs are completed
successfully,
then the status in the job run stash
table would be updated to complete.
If one or more jobs have failed,
the status is updated to fail and a
notification will be sent out based upon
the based on on the status of the batch.
OK let me show you here also in the low
seat also it is same.
It will check if all the jobs under this
batch has succeeded.
If all that that succeeded,
it will just update the status to
completed in the batch runsters and
success notification would be send out if
it is.
If if all the jobs are not succeeded then
it would update the status as failed and
it will send out a failure notification.
So in that case inside a batch,
if there are 10 jobs,
1011 notification will be sent, Yeah,
for 10,
for 10 individual job runs and extra 1
for batch, overall batch.
That is huge because on everyday basis it
is expected to have the successful run
only, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Like I think it's a client requirement.
Also they didn't write like we have a
walkthrough of code with client already.
Like explicitly while sending out
notification or making an entrance into
this,
they ask a few parameters that needs to
be like that needs to be present for sure
like batch name, job names.
I tell if we're not passing them,
we are just passing the job ID, batch ID,
job run ID, exception run ID.
These details only we usually pass right?
But they explicitly ask.
Then we have added them again as part of
free work after the feedback.
OK, OK.
It's taking so long.
Sometimes this VDI irritates.
Oh my God,
why aren't we not able to do let me open
it in the Microsoft.
What happened?
Should I sign in another move?
Huh?
I don't know that is your.
Is IDMC open from your end?
Oh my God,
let me know if it is open from your end.
There is something issue with my
otherwise let me disconnect and connect
it again.
Hello.
Yeah is it open?
Yeah,
you can share your screen and show me the
batch task flow.
Open any batch task flow account D go to
explore type Dai.
Open Dai account main main search for
batch pillow one.
First one is batch prerequisite.
So scroll to the left,
I'll tell you scroll to a little left.
So in the start strip,
we have two temporary parameters which
are temporary count and batch status,
temporary error count user to count the
failures of the jobs within the batch.
Temporary batch status is the final batch
status which would be use it to send out
notification and also update the status
in the batch run stats.
OK,
So once we'll add this assignment task
under each and every like under each and
every subtask loop.
And here we would be updating it to one
in case of a failure.
OK, next in the dash and task.
Next in the dash and task we will not
this not this before that we have just
after the subtask, we have this one.
OK, so here decision task,
we'll check if the error count is equal
to 0.
If it is equal to 0,
it means no job has failed in that run.
This has to be kept after all the subtask
flows are arranged in as per their run
order and here if it is equal to 0 we
will set the batch run status to
completed or success.
Click on the assignment task after that
at zero in the first part here we are
come like assigning C tour.
If it is space we are assigning FI guess
below 1F and then in the batch run starts
we are passing this as a one of the input
field OK times batch status OK open this
batch task mapping task,
open the mapping OK copy the query from
here.
So here we are just trying to get using
the input batch ID and status has started.
We are trying to fast the latest batch
run ID, so we have to upgrade it, right?
And then current time stamp value and
audit summary failed.
OK,
we are just trying to get the latest
batch run ID along with audit columns.
Yeah, that's it.
You can go to the next, next,
next transformation in the mark.
So here we are updating setting the value
for status.
If my temporary input state,
parent status,
whatever we are passing here right?
If it is C then it is completed otherwise
it is failed.
Using all these values,
we will be updating the batch run strats.
I'm going to directly go to fill mapping
using batch run ID.
Batch run ID is a picky column.
We are using it for update operation and
we are updating it batch run ID OK we are
updating batch end time status audit,
update item audit up by that's true and
go to the task once batch transfer.
Once this is done using the same status,
we have another decision task,
print decision task.
So here if my batch status equal to C,
success notification would be sent out.
If it is,
if failure notification would be sent out.
And if,
if any failure notification is sent out,
we have we are failing the task load
after sending it.
OK, yeah, that's it.
Raya, could you please go to the LLD once?
I'll just give you a high level of error
handling, manual handling,
all those things.
All that we get down error handling
folder.
Yeah.
So here the prerequisite process fails if
the latest target job June batch run is
not completed.
OK, so we have a batch predict site.
It is a separate task flow.
I told you it in the first KTV KT call I
guess.
So we have it it it will get failed and
it it,
it it gets failed if if my if our target
the latest shown batch that's not
completed.
OK,
interrupted batch runs in starter status
or marker in failure fail before restart.
OK.
So any batch run interrupted due to
network failure.
So if in case if any batch run got
interrupted due to network failure,
its status would be started right?
We have to update like it will be updated
as fail before reset.
We have to update it as failed and we
have to start the task flow batch run OK
Failed batch runs are restarted using the
same execution right?
We will be using same execution run ID
for restart purpose.
Successfully completed jobs are skipped
during during restart OK and target
cleanup is performed before restart
automatically OK restart.
What I mean to say is before restart load,
target cleanup would be done and job
execution failures are recorded in the
job error stats log.
That this I told you right?
And then failed or invalid source loads
caused the target job to like to fail, OK.
This is the part of ETL execution log.
So this is part of batch job preload
failed or invalid source load.
So any source load gets failed,
we won't be going with the target job
load, right?
So that is the reason why we are failing.
We are updating the status in the job run
status failed OK.
The next one is critical validation
failures prevent impacted record from
loading into the target.
So if any critical validation check fail,
we are not loading them into the target.
Informational valid validation failures
are logged,
but the records continue to load.
Can you add can you can you add continue
to load into the target?
Continue to load into the target small it
is OK,
into the target OK Reconciliation
failures or out of balance threshold
metrics cause the job to fail.
OK.
This is balance related to balance to
cancellation.
If any method is out of threshold,
then it's a failure.
We will be failing the job.
Main load failures mark the job and
related rule executions as failed.
I told you right, if anything is failed,
we would be updating rule execution log
and job run stress, right?
So I mean that the batches failed if one
or more jobs failed.
This this you know and manual handling
the batch pre requisite task for must be
manually trigger if the latest job run
batch is not not completed.
What what I mean to say is if my batch
start OK, batch pre requisite OK,
if my latest zone 2 batch is not
completed then in that case batch pre
requisite will be failed right after
updating it to either completed or
bypassing this batch prerequisite,
we have to run our actual batch OK.
This this should be the batch
prerequisite that's not completed
completed after after making after making
it either to after updating it to
completed as per the scenario.
Otherwise we can directly run the batch.
We can directly trigger OK,
manual trigger if OK, OK, RIA here.
I think complete information is not
provided.
What I mean to say here is if my latest
batch is not in completed state then my
batch to request a task for would be
failed.
In that case I would this end like the
admin team will get our notification what
they have to do.
Either they have to update the status to
complete it and trigger this batch to
request a task for directly.
Otherwise,
if it is in failed status and if they are
OK to run, restart, do a reset or rerun,
they can directly trigger the batch.
Batch task flow.
OK I get this segment is is the batch
free request OK?
The batch free request the task flow must
be manually trigger if the latest zone 2
batch is not completed after updating the
status to completed.
You can write just after updating the
status to completed.
Keep check updating spelling.
Otherwise, if like otherwise OK,
otherwise they can do,
we can skip this and directly go with the
with the restart or rerun based upon the
like failure or failure scenario or like
that directly proceed with the with
either restart or rerun based upon the
data issue or based upon the issue task.
Look for restart or rerun store rerun
based upon the failure or based upon the
failure.
You can write based upon the failure.
OK, not failure, right?
Rerun is not dependent upon failure.
It can be or cannot be, right,
but then can you?
So, yeah.
So one thing, OK, based upon the scenario,
yeah, yeah, I'll tell.
Yeah, based upon the scenario,
that is fine for restart.
And the second point is for restart
return or return return scenarios,
the target zone batch task flow must be
triggered manually.
So this is not a prerequisite.
We don't touch prerequisite task for
these three scenarios.
We will be directly triggering the target
zone batch task flow.
OK,
rerun and zone 1 rerun in case rerun
reports must be created manually with
required execution details in the batch
run strikes.
OK,
like what does it mean Like not only
rerun, zone 1 rerun,
you can also add first time history catch
up first time incremental also before
rerun.
Before rerun history catch up.
First time incremental.
OK.
Before the batsman said remove 1 space,
keep only one space, remove that.
OK, Remove one more.
OK.
Keep only one space, keep 1 space.
Yeah, right.
Is it OK?
It is happening.
Space.
OK, OK, cool.
OK, required sourcing dates for.
OK next required sourcing dates and
parameter values must be provided for
rerun processing.
OK for rerun we have to get the execution
run ID from the parameter file right?
So those days should be provided for
rerun processing.
Restart or rerun must be performed only
after validation.
So if if any error comes or any failure
occurs this these two needs to be
performed only after validation.
Target cleanup must be performed manually
for reader OK and then notification.
Notification is sent when batch requests
like task flow fails, process fails,
OK and,
and failure notification is sent out for
source load failures and critical
validation failures,
record count or record balance
reconciliation failures,
information validation failures to
balance differences within the alert
threshold and,
and when the job completes successfully
when with all cheques passed and final
batch notification.
All these are the notification stuff.
How many notifications are we set like
scenarios when the notification should be
sent?
OK, I think we are, we are, we are on.
Are we having any details in the No, no,
we are, we are on the last page of it.
OK,
I think we are done with the technical
slide.
Let's stop the record.